{
    "subject": "resource/Zagreb",
    "predicate": "property/janRecordHighC",
    "object": "19.4",
    "human_readable": "Zagreb's January record high temperature is 19.4.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9237635135650635,
            "question": "What is the record high temperature for January in Zagreb?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8787552118301392,
            "question": "Is it possible for temperatures to reach above 19 degrees Celsius in Zagreb during January?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8321974873542786,
            "question": "Could you survive outdoors in Zagreb without proper clothing during January if it reached 19.4 degrees Celsius?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8293745517730713,
            "question": "What is the highest temperature that Zagreb has ever recorded in January?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8165528178215027,
            "question": "What temperature is considered the extreme high for January in Zagreb?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7262990474700928,
            "question": "Are there any months where Zagreb experiences higher temperatures than January?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7232803106307983,
            "question": "What is the average temperature in Zagreb during January?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.683150589466095,
            "question": "How hot can it get in Zagreb during January?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6625909209251404,
            "question": "In what month does Zagreb experience its highest temperatures?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3638169765472412,
            "question": "Does Zagreb have a mild climate for its location?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Zagreb's January record high temperature is 19.4.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7575_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what month does Zagreb experience its highest temperatures?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7575_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How hot can it get in Zagreb during January?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7575_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the average temperature in Zagreb during January?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7575_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7575_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7575_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7575_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7575_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7575_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7575_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7575_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7575_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7575_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7575_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\nThe provided text states that the highest recorded temperature in Zagreb for January was 15\u00b0C (which is equal to 59\u00b0F). It does not mention a record high of 19.4 degrees.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about the weather conditions and climate of Zagreb, including its average temperatures in January. However, they do not specify a precise record high temperature for January. The closest information provided is that the highest recorded temperature in January can be as low as -1\u00b0C (2009) or 15\u00b0C (2014), but there's no mention of a specific record high of 19.4\u00b0C."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}